<resources>
    <string name="app_name">THRYVE</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="student_email">"student@sheridancollege.ca"</string>
    <string name="student_login">"First Last"</string>
    <string name="registration">"Registration"</string>
    <string name="c_register">"Complete Registration"</string>
    <string name="first_name">"First Name"</string>
    <string name="last_name">"Last Name"</string>
    <string name="sheridan_email">"Sheridan E-mail Address"</string>
    <string name="password">"Password"</string>
    <string name="re_type_password">"Re-type Password"</string>

    <string name="plan_your_edu_body_text">"Take advantage of these services and resources to explore options, set goals, and make the educational plans to achieve them."</string>
    <string name="plan_your_career_body_text">"Services and online tools to help you select the right Sheridan program or map out education beyond graduation in your current program."</string>
    <string name="cocurricular_body_text">"Services and online tools to help you select the right Sheridan program or map out education beyond graduation in your current program."</string>
    <string name="find_work_body_text">"Whether you’re looking for job opportunities, preparing for an interview, or developing your portfolio, the Career Centre is here to help."</string>
    <string name="visit_centre_body_text">"Visit the Career Centre at your local campus to find more information."</string>

    <string name="quicktips_first_text">"A gateway to our picks for immediately-useful online resources for career exploration and educational planning."</string>
    <string name="cruising_first_text">"Career Cruising is an interactive career planning resource with detailed descriptions of what people do in 600+ different Canadian occupations, as well as other career and educational planning tools."</string>
    <string name="microcourse_first_text">"This course walks you through all the way from self-assessment to career exploration to educational planning.</string>
    <string name="talkCounselor_first_text">"Career Counsellors are available to current students and grads to help you explore career options, set career goals, research labour market information, and plan further education."</string>

    <string name="ccr_string1">"Sheridan’s Co-Curricular Record (CCR) program provides students with the opportunity to get involved in their community, make a difference, meet new people, and develop new skills and experiences that are valued by employers."</string>
    <string name="ccr_string2">"Students have the opportunity to create a CCR record to document their out-of-classroom learning experiences while completing their academic studies. Students and alumni can use their CCR record, which is an official Sheridan document, to showcase their professional development to employers."</string>
    <string name="ccr_string3">"Employers value out-of-classroom experiences and community involvement when hiring students and graduates, having a CCR record is concrete evidence of your motivation to take responsibility for your learning and professional development."</string>
    <string name="ccr_string4">"A CCR record can also be used as supporting documentation for application packages for employment, for further post-secondary/graduate school and for scholarships and bursary applications."</string>
    <string name="ccr_string5">"Current Sheridan students: Login to Access Sheridan, select the link “MySheridanCo-Curricular”"</string>
    <string name="ccr_string6">"Visit the public CCR website: https://mysheridanccr.sheridancollege.ca/home.htm"</string>
    <string name="ccr_string7">"For more information about Sheridan’s CCR, contact us directly at: mysheridanccr@sheridancollege.ca"</string>
</resources>
